Web Developer

32 St Quintin Road **Plaistow** London UK E13 9DT

Contact

geraldjtorres@gmail.com 077 4077 5082 @geraldjtorres



My name is Gerald Torres. Having studied Multimedia Computing in University, I have been able to gain and develop the fundamental skills and knowledge required within the Web Development industry. My hunger for expanding my learning has lead me up to date with the latest and ever-growing web development technologies such as HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript which are essential for any website.

As a Web Developer, I have a passion for ensuring the user has great User Experience and I believe this is the most important requirement of any project. I believe that excellent interactivity between the user and the website is what makes it a success.



#### EDUCATION.

Anticipating graduation - 2015 University of Westminster Multimedia Computing

2009 - 2011

St. Angela's & St. Bonaventure's Sixth Form College **Computer Science Product Design** 

Media



## **WORK EXPERIENCE.**

July 2013 - September 2013 Model Abercrombie & Fitch Seattle WA, USA

September 2014 - Present Freelance Web Developer

London UK

December 2014 - Present

Front End Developer/Web Designer

Foxtons London UK



## TECHNICAL SKILLS.

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript **JQuery** AJAX

Photoshop Illustrator After Effects **Premier Pro** 

Web Usability Responsive Design Interactive Design





#### PERSONAL SKILLS.

Personality Team Player, Innovative, Creative

Organisation Planning, Strategy, Communication

Empathic, Honest, Open-minded

Resilience Motivated, Inspired, Willingess to lean



# ONLINE.

Online Portfolio www.geraldtorres.co.uk

My Skill List

www.teamtreehouse.com/geraldtorres

My Success story

https://teamtreehouse.com/stories/gerald-torres

LinkedIn Profile

www.linkedin.com/pub/gerald-torres/94/24a/92a

### **HOBBIES & INTERESTS.**















Film

Photography

Comics

Gaming

Music

**Fitness** 

Travel